Juanita Kidd Stout Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Legal File, 1873-1997 (Box 24-75)
  - Court of Common Pleas, Philadelphia County, Pa.
    - Case file
      - Criminal cases
        - Commonwealth v. Gallo, 1985-1993 (Box 42)
        - Commonwealth v. Garcia, 1984-1985
        - Commonwealth v. Garcia, 1986-1987
        - Commonwealth v. Gatewood, 1985-1993
        - Commonwealth v. Gay, 1972
        - Commonwealth v. Gay, 1976-1979, 1986
        - Commonwealth v. Gilbert, 1976
        - Commonwealth v. Goldsmith, 1992-1993
        - Commonwealth v. Gonzalez, 1982-1983
        - Commonwealth v. Gonzales, 1985-1986
        - Commonwealth v. Gray, 1986-1989
        - Commonwealth v. Green, 1985-1987
        - Commonwealth v. Green, 1992-1997
        - Commonwealth v. Griswold, 1996
        - Commonwealth v. Haas, 1979-1980
        - Commonwealth v. Harris, 1970-1971
        - Commonwealth v. Harris, 1974-1976
        - Commonwealth v. Harris, 1982-1988
        - Commonwealth v. Hawkins, 1971-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Hayman, 1982
        - Commonwealth v. Helm, 1976
        - Commonwealth v. Henderson, 1973
        - Commonwealth v. Henderson, 1981-1982
        - Commonwealth v. Henderson, 1987
        - Commonwealth v. Hendricks, 1974-1975
        - Commonwealth v. Hightower, 1983-1984, 1991
        - Commonwealth v. Hill, 1976-1978
        - Commonwealth v. Hill, 1980-1981, 1991
        - Commonwealth v. Hines, 1980-1981
        - Commonwealth v. Holley, 1982, 1996 (Box 43)
        - Commonwealth v. Holmes, 1970-1972
        - Commonwealth v. Horner, 1977-1979
        - Commonwealth v. Howard, 1981-1985
        - Commonwealth v. Howell, 1983-1984
        - Commonwealth v. Hudson, 1970-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Huertas, 1983-1984
        - Commonwealth v. Humphrey, 1971-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Hunter, 1970-1972
        - Commonwealth v. Hyers, 1967-1969
        - Commonwealth v. Issac, 1978-1979
        - Commonwealth v. Jackson, 1967-1969
        - Commonwealth v. Jackson, 1970-1971
        - Commonwealth v. Jackson, 1972-1974
        - Commonwealth v. Jackson, 1974-1975
        - Commonwealth v. Jackson, 1980-1981, 1987
        - Commonwealth v. Jackson, 1985-1988
        - Commonwealth v. Jacobs, 1972
        - Commonwealth v. Jacobson, 1970, 1971
        - Commonwealth v. James, 1982-1983
        - Commonwealth v. James, 1980-1981
        - Commonwealth v. James, 1994
        - Commonwealth v. Jamison, 1979, 1992
        - Commonwealth v. Jarvis, 1975
        - Commonwealth v. Jefferson, 1968, 1976, 1990-1991
        - Commonwealth v. Jefferson, 1982-1983
        - Commonwealth v. Jenkins, 1972-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Johnson, 1972-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Johnson, 1976, 1980-1981
        - Commonwealth v. Johnson, 1988-1989
        - Commonwealth v. Johnson, 1993
        - Commonwealth v. Jones, 1971-1972
        - Commonwealth v. Jones, 1974 (Box 44)
        - Commonwealth v. Jones, 1975-1976
        - Commonwealth v. Jones, 1978-1979
        - Commonwealth v. Jones, 1981-1982
        - Commonwealth v. Jones, 1986
          - Chronological file, 1986-1997, undated
          - Sentencing reports, 1987
        - Commonwealth v. Jones, 1988
        - Commonwealth v. Jones, 1988-1991
        - Commonwealth v. Kennedy, 1976-1977
        - Commonwealth v. Kettrles, 1972-1974
        - Commonwealth v. Knox, 1970
        - Commonwealth v. Lare, 1979-1980
        - Commonwealth v. Lawrence, 1978-1980, 1995-1997
        - Commonwealth v. Lawson, 1980-1981
        - Commonwealth v. Lee, 1970, 1977
        - Commonwealth v. Long, 1986-1993
        - Commonwealth v. Loper, 1993
        - Commonwealth v. Lowe, 1972-1974
        - Commonwealth v. Lozado, 1984-1985, 1997
        - Commonwealth v. Lucas, 1985-1988
        - Commonwealth v. Mack, 1969-1971
        - Commonwealth v. Marinelli, 1996-1997 (Box 45)
        - Commonwealth v. Matthews, 1975
        - Commonwealth v. Matthews, 1979-1982
        - Commonwealth v. Maxwell, 1980-1982
        - Commonwealth v. Mayes, 1977
        - Commonwealth v. McAndrews, 1977-1979
        - Commonwealth v. McCallum, 1990
        - Commonwealth v. McCloud, 1977-1978
        - Commonwealth v. McConnell, 1980-1981
        - Commonwealth v. McGrath, 1984
        - Commonwealth v. McGruder, 1996-1997
        - Commonwealth v. McKee, 1978
        - Commonwealth v. NcNeill, 1980-1981
        - Commonwealth v. Medina, 1991-1992
        - Commonwealth v. Miller, 1984-1986
        - Commonwealth v. Mims, 1984
        - Commonwealth v. Mincy, 1974-1975
        - Commonwealth v. Mitchell, 1984-1989
        - Commonwealth v. Mizell, 1974-1978, 1984
        - Commonwealth v. Moore, 1971-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Mora, 1983-1984
        - Commonwealth v. Morrison, 1971-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Morton, 1974-1978
        - Commonwealth v. Murphy, 1981-1982
        - Commonwealth v. Myers, 1972
        - Commonwealth v. Neal, 1968-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Newton, 1968-1969
        - Commonwealth v. Oakie, 1976-1978
        - Commonwealth v. O'Brien, 1972-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Ogrod, 1993-1994, undated
        - Commonwealth v. Osorio, 1972-1973 (Box 46)
        - Commonwealth v. Pabon, 1986-1991
        - Commonwealth v. Palmer, 1970-1972
        - Commonwealth v. Patterson, 1991
        - Commonwealth v. Petcher, 1971
        - Commonwealth v. Philisten, 1995, undated
        - Commonwealth v. Pirela, 1982-1986, 1995 See also Container 48, Commonwealth v. Tirado
        - Commonwealth v. Polite, 1992-1993
        - Commonwealth v. Poplar, 1980-1981
        - Commonwealth v. Poulos, 1969-1970
        - Commonwealth v. Ransom, 1975-1977, 1988
        - Commonwealth v. Ransome, 1985
        - Commonwealth v. Reaves, 1982-1984, 1992
        - Commonwealth v. Refile, 1981-1985, 1993
        - Commonwealth v. Riggins, 1970-1971
        - Commonwealth v. Rios, 1987, 1997, undated
        - Commonwealth v. Roane, 1984-1987
        - Commonwealth v. Robinson, 1981-1984, 1997
        - Commonwealth v. Robinson, 1990-1993
        - Commonwealth v. Rodgers, 1971
        - Commonwealth v. Rodriguez, 1991-1992
        - Commonwealth v. Rosado, 1984
        - Commonwealth v. Ross, 1980
        - Commonwealth v. Roux, 1973-1975 (Box 47)
        - Commonwealth v. Russell, 1973-1974
        - Commonwealth v. Ryan, 1975-circa 1980
        - Commonwealth v. Sampson, 1968-1970
        - Commonwealth v. Sanford, 1984-1986
        - Commonwealth v. Santiago, 1970-1971
        - Commonwealth v. Santiago, 1973-1975, 1987
        - Commonwealth v. Santiago, 1991
        - Commonwealth v. Saunders, 1973-1974
        - Commonwealth v. Saunders, 1981-1983
        - Commonwealth v. Scott, 1980-1981
        - Commonwealth v. Scott, 1983-1987
        - Commonwealth v. Scott, 1986-1988
        - Commonwealth v. Seabrook, 1975-1976
        - Commonwealth v. Selby, 1986-1991
        - Commonwealth v. Shoats, 1972
          - Chronological file, 1972-1980, 1991
          - Newspaper clippings, 1972-1980, (2 folders)
          - Opinions, 1972
          - Shoats, Sharon, 1972-1976, undated
        - Commonwealth v. Simms, 1973-1974
        - Commonwealth v. Small, 1975-1976
        - Commonwealth v. Smith, 1996
        - Commonwealth v. Smith, 1983-1984
        - Commonwealth v. Smith, 1975-1976
        - Commonwealth v. Sockel, 1976
        - Commonwealth v. Staples, 1976-1978 (Box 48)
        - Commonwealth v. Stokes, 1976-1977
        - Commonwealth v. Stokes, 1982
        - Commonwealth v. Strand, 1972
        - Commonwealth v. Strickland, 1985-1994
        - Commonwealth v. Sturgis, 1986-1987, 1996
        - Commonwealth v. Stutzer, 1978-1980
        - Commonwealth v. Styles, 1978-1979, 1992
        - Commonwealth v. Sutton, 1981
        - Commonwealth v. Taylor, 1972-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Thomas, 1971, 1997
        - Commonwealth v. Thomas, 1976, 1987
        - Commonwealth v. Thomas, 1981-1982, 1997
        - Commonwealth v. Thomas, 1985
        - Commonwealth v. Thompson, 1972-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Tillman, 1980
        - Commonwealth v. Tirado, 1982, 1990-1995 See also Container 46, Commonwealth v. Pirela
        - Commonwealth v. Tomlinson, 1970
        - Commonwealth v. Truesdale, 1976-1979
        - Commonwealth v. Truesdale, 1983-1986, 1991
        - Commonwealth v. Tucker, 1981
        - Commonwealth v. Turner, 1972
        - Commonwealth v. Velasquez, 1979-1981
        - Commonwealth v. Walker, 1979-1981
        - Commonwealth v. Walker, 1984-1987
        - Commonwealth v. Wallace, 1973-1974
        - Commonwealth v. Wallace, 1985
        - Commonwealth v. Warren, 1973
        - Commonwealth v. Warren, 1974-1976
        - Commonwealth v. Washington, 1971-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Washington, 1972-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Washington, 1979-1980
        - Commonwealth v. Waters, 1979-1981, 1991
        - Commonwealth v. Weaver, 1976-1978
        - Commonwealth v. Wells, 1990
        - Commonwealth v. Wheeler, 1979-1980
        - Commonwealth v. White, 1968-1970
        - Commonwealth v. White, 1975-1977 (Box 49)
        - Commonwealth v. White, 1975-1977
        - Commonwealth v. White
          - Pardon hearings, 1975, 1982-1993, undated
          - Trial, 1975
        - Commonwealth v. White, 1977-1978
        - Commonwealth v. White, 1981, 1991
        - Commonwealth v. White, 1981
        - Commonwealth v. White, 1982-1984
        - Commonwealth v. White, 1992
        - Commonwealth v. Wicks, 1972-1973
        - Commonwealth v. Williams, 1979-1980, 1986-1988
        - Commonwealth v. Williams, 1985
        - Commonwealth v. Williams, 1986
        - Commonwealth v. Williams, 1987
        - Commonwealth v. Williams, 1987-1989
        - Commonwealth v. Williams, 1996
        - Commonwealth v. Wise, 1979, 1988
        - Commonwealth v. Wittick, 1981-1983, 1990
        - Commonwealth v. Woodward See Container 70, Stout v. W. W. Norton & Co.
        - Commonwealth v. Wright, 1978-1979
        - Commonwealth v. Wyatt, 1990-1995
        - Commonwealth v. Wyche, 1969-1972
        - Commonwealth v. Wyche, 1991-1995
        - Commonwealth v. Young, 1978-1981, 1992-1995
        - Commonwealth v. Young, 1981-1982
        - Commonwealth v. Zayas, 1989-1991
        - Commonwealth v. Zukauskas, 1979-1980
        - First degree murder cases, proportionality reviews, 1991-1994, undated
        - Judge's trial notes, undated, (2 folders) (Box 50)
        - Miscellaneous cases
          - Commonwealth v. Abney-Commonwealth v. Murray, 1970-1997, (4 folders)
          - Commonwealth v. Nichols-Commonwealth v. Young, 1972-1997, (3 folders) (Box 51)
          - Unidentified cases, 1990, undated
    - Grand juries
      - 1974, January term
      - 1975, August, September-October terms
      - 1986, May term, MOVE investigation
        - Charges and instructions to jury, 1986
        - Extension of term, 1987
        - Juror list, 1986
        - Motion for recusal of presiding judge, 1986
        - Motion to disqualify law firm of Mozenter, Molloy, and Durst, 1986-1987
        - Mulvihill, Terrence P., and Lawrence D'Ulisse, claims of privilege, 1986 (Box 52)
        - Newspaper clippings, 1986-1987
        - Opening statements by assistant district attorneys, 1986
        - Philadelphia Special Investigation Commission on MOVE, 1985-1986
        - Voir dire, 1986
        - Witnesses
          - Miscellaneous, 1986-1987
          - Rendell, Edward, 1986
  - District Attorney's Office, Philadelphia County
    - Abraham, Lynne, letter to Maxwell E. P. King, Philadelphia Inquirer, 1992
    - Case file
      - Commonwealth v. Wilson
        - Appeal, 1957
        - Newspaper clippings, 1958, 1985
        - Trial, 1957
      - Superior Court, Pennsylvania
        - Briefs, 1956-1959, (2 folders)
        - Lists of cases, 1957-1964 (Box 53)
      - Supreme Court, Pennsylvania
        - Briefs, 1956-1958
        - Commonwealth v. De Moss, 1959
        - Commonwealth v. Graves, 1958
        - Lists of cases, 1958-1959
    - “Individuals Sentenced to Electric Chair from Philadelphia County,” 1958
    - Miscellany, 1956-1961, 1977, undated
    - Printed matter, 1959-1961 (Box 54)
  - Estates
    - Alexander, Sadie T. M. See also Container 77, Biographical file
      - Chronological file
        - 1983, Oct.-1990, Dec., (9 folders)
        - 1991, Jan.-1997, Nov., (9 folders) (Box 55)
      - Tanner, Henry O., 1983-1992, undated
      - Wills, 1969-1977
    - Coleman, Nora, 1980-1984 (Box 56)
    - Wilson, Juanita, 1990-1992
  - Municipal Court, Philadelphia County, Pa.
    - Case file
      - Cases appealed, 1966
      - Commonwealth ex rel. Howell v. Howell, 1961-1962
      - Commonwealth ex rel. Kaminski v. Kosinski, 1961
      - Commonwealth ex rel. Kane v. Kane, 1962
      - Commonwealth ex rel. Middleman v. Middleman, 1965-1968, 1989-1990
      - Commonwealth ex rel. Miller v. Dillworth, 1964-1965
      - Commonwealth ex rel. Taylor v. Taylor, undated
      - Commonwealth ex rel. Weisburg v. Weisburg, 1960
      - Commonwealth Alexander, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth Appolloni, 1964, 1997, undated
      - Commonwealth Armstrong, 1968
      - Commonwealth v. Beck, 1961-1962
      - Commonwealth v. Benson, 1967
      - Commonwealth v. Britt, 1961
      - Commonwealth v. Clipper, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth v. DaTore, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth v. Fields, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth v. Davis, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth v. Goldstein, 1965-1968
      - Commonwealth v. Green, 1966-1967
      - Commonwealth v. Jackson, 1967
      - Commonwealth v. Johnson, 1968-1969
      - Commonwealth v. Miller, 1966-1969
      - Commonwealth v. Miller, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth v. Mills, 1993-1994
      - Commonwealth v. Moore, 1966-1969
      - Commonwealth v. Overstreight and Commonwealth v. Hicks, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth v. Parker, 1967
      - Commonwealth v. Richardson, 1966 (Box 57)
      - Commonwealth v. Rozanski, 1962-1965
      - Commonwealth v. Sears, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth v. Slackus, 1964
      - Commonwealth v. Vaughn, 1967-1968
      - Commonwealth v. West, 1967
      - Commonwealth v. Zeigler, 1967-1968
      - Brown v. American Casualty Co., 1961-1964
      - Dluge v. Robinson, 1964
      - Miscellaneous cases, 1959-1964, undated
      - Moore v. Bauer, 1963
      - Staley v. Salvesen, 1963
    - Consumer fraud
      - Correspondence, 1964-1968, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1961-1965, undated, (4 folders)
    - Docket, 1962-1964 See Oversize
    - Induction, 1959 (Box 58)
    - Juvenile offenders
      - Gangs, 1963-1968
      - Girls
        - Diablos gang
          - Chronological file, 1961-1965, undated, (2 folders)
          - Educational and career development material, 1962, undated
          - Essays and reports assigned by Stout, 1961-1962, undated
          - Newspaper clippings, 1961-1962, undated
        - Fund for Three Teenagers, 1964-1969, undated
    - Miscellany, 1961-1967, undated
  - Pennsylvania judicial elections
    - Chronological file
      - 1959, July-1966, Apr., (5 folders)
      - 1966, May-1987, July, (9 folders) (Box 59)
    - Miscellany, 1959-1966, undated
    - Newspapers, 1969
    - Stout v. Helm, 1966-1967
  - Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission, allegation of racial discrimination by taxicab driver against Stout, 1969 (Box 60)
  - Printed matter
    - Authentication of sound recordings, 1958, undated
    - Bail, undated
    - Cases
      - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania
        - Adult criminal
          - Commonwealth v. Abdullah-Commonwealth v. Smith, 1939-1995, (9 folders)
          - Commonwealth v. Taylor-Commonwealth v. Young, 1977-1995, (2 folders) (Box 61)
        - Juvenile criminal, 1991-1992, undated
      - Other states, 1984-1994
      - United States
        - District courts, 1951-1993, undated
        - Supreme Court
          - Alphabetical file, Arizona v. Roberson-Wong Sun v. United States, 1873, 1941-1991, (3 folders)
          - Lists (Box 62)
    - Commonwealth of Pennsylvania
      - Miscellany, 1958, 1982-1983, 1992, undated
      - Uniform Crime Report, 1994, (2 folders)
    - DNA and blood evidence, 1982-1992, undated, (2 folders)
    - Flag desecration and free speech, undated
    - Insanity defense, 1985, undated
    - Judges and courts, 1974-1992, undated, (3 folders) (Box 63)
    - Labor law, 1975, undated
    - Lawyers and the legal profession, 1890, 1957-1963, 1973-1992, undated, (4 folders)
    - Older Americans and crime, 1987, undated (Box 64)
    - Pennsylvania courts and judges, newspaper clippings, 1961-1997, undated, (7 folders)
    - Peremptory challenges, 1990, undated
    - Philadelphia, Pa., courts, guides, directories, and organizational charts, 1977-1994, undated (Box 65)
    - Press and media issues
      - Cases, 1972-1990, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1982-1990, undated
    - Pretrial identification, undated
    - Prisoners and prison issues, 1979, undated
    - Search and seizure, undated
    - Self-defense, undated
    - Sentencing, 1995, undated
    - Sex crimes (Box 66)
      - Miscellany, circa 1958
      - Myers, John E. B., Expert Testimony in Child Sexual Abuse Litigation, 1987
    - Space law, 1967, 1982-1984, undated
    - U. S. Department of Justice, 1978-1979
    - Women's issues, 1975
  - Professional associations
    - American Bar Association
      - American Bar Foundation Fellows, 1991-1995, undated
      - Fund for Justice and Education, 1992-1997
      - Judicial Administration Division, 1982-1993, undated
      - Minorities in the Profession Commission, 1981
      - Miscellany, 1970-1993, undated, (2 folders)
    - American Judges Association, 1982, 1989-1994, undated (Box 67)
    - American Judicature Society, 1979-1980, undated
    - Association of Black Lawyers of Westchester County, N.Y., 1984
    - Miscellaneous associations, 1970-1996, undated
    - National Association of Women Judges
      - Chronological file, 1984-1992
      - Membership directories, 1983-1985
      - Newsletters, 1983-1987
    - National Association of Women Lawyers
      - Alaska Bar Rag, 1983
      - Chronological file, 1968, 1982-1985, undated
      - Women Lawyers Journal, 1983-1985
    - National Bar Association (Box 68)
      - Chronological file, 1981-1994, undated
      - Judicial Council
        - Miscellany, 1984-1988, undated
        - National Roster of Black Judicial Officers, 1980
      - Printed matter
        - Membership directory, 1970
        - Miscellany, 1983-1985
        - National Bar Bulletin, 1986-1988
      - Women's Division, Philadelphia, Pa., chapter, 1982-1992
    - National Conference of Black Lawyers, 1984
    - North Carolina Association of Black Lawyers, African-American Female Pioneers in Search of Justice and Equality 1947-1990
    - Pennsylvania Bar Association, 1973-1987, 1997 (Box 69)
    - Philadelphia Bar Association
      - African American members list, 1962-1972, undated
      - Barristers' Association
        - Barristers' Association Reporter, 1991-1993
        - Chronological file, 1983-1997, undated
        - Hastie, William H., Barristers' Club dinner in his honor, 1969
      - Membership directories, 1955-1967
      - Miscellany, 1969-1997
      - Special Committee on Racial Bias in the Justice System
        - Briefs, 1993
        - Correspondence and members list, 1993-1995 (Box 70)
        - Reports, 1993
    - Temple Inn of Court, 1990
  - Stout v. W. W. Norton & Co.
    - Chronological file, 1995, (2 folders)
    - Commonwealth v. Woodward
      - Correspondence, 1984-1991
      - Memoranda, 1984-1992
      - Miscellany, 1984, undated
      - Newspaper clippings, 1984-1993, undated
      - Opinions, 1984-1992
      - Other cases, 1937, 1973-1993, undated
      - Testimony, 1984
    - Correspondence
      - 1995, Mar.-Dec., (2 folders)
      - 1996, Jan.-1997, Sept., undated (Box 71)
    - Miscellany, 1990-1992, undated
    - Motion for remand packet, 1995
    - Other cases, 1964, 1982-1995, undated
    - Washington, Linn
      - Black Judges on Justice. New York, 1994
      - Correspondence and newspaper clippings, 1992-1997, undated
  - Supreme court, Pennsylvania
    - Appellate Judges Education Subcommittee, 1988
    - Case file
      - Calendars and lists of cases, 1988-1989
      - in re Braig, 1987-1989
      - in re Horgos, 1996
      - in re Larson, 1988
      - Miscellaneous cases, 1988-1989
      - in re Stout, 1989 (Box 72)
        - Correspondence, 1989-1996
        - Newspaper clippings, 1989, undated
        - General case material, 1989, (2 folders)
        - Opinions, 1989
        - Rules of appellate procedure, undated
      - in re Sylvester, 1985-1989, (3 folders)
    - Correspondence, 1980, 1988-1989, undated
    - Dockets (Box 73)
      - 1988
      - 1989 (Box 74)
    - Induction ceremony, 1988 (Box 75)
    - Orders, 1991, 1997
    - Employees, 1988-1989
    - Miscellany, 1987-1989, undated
    - Report on the Operational Review of the Administrative Office of the Pennsylvania Courts, 1988
  - United States Court of Appeal for the Third Circuit, vacancy
    - Correspondence, 1977-1978
    - Resumés and biographical sketches, 1974-1978, undated
    - Sample opinions and other writings, 1976-1979, undated
    - Stout v. Helm and related material, 1966, undated
- Subject File, circa 1900-1998 (Box 75-93)
  Printed matter, photographs, correspondence, organizational records, and miscellaneous material.
  Arranged alphabetically by subject or type of material and thereunder chronologically.
  - African American architects in Philadelphia, Pa., 1995, undated (Box 75)
  - Alzheimer's Association, 1982-1996, undated
  - American Association of University Women, 1980-1996
  - American Management Association, 1966, undated
  - American Red Cross, Southeastern Pennsylvania chapter, 1985-1992, undated
  - Association of Business and Professional Women of Philadelphia and Vicinity, 1979
  - Biographical file (Box 76)
    - “A” miscellaneous, 1981-1988
    - Battles, Jonathan, 1986, undated
    - “B” miscellaneous, 1936, 1977-1984, 1996
    - Carolina, Valerie I., 1973, 1985, undated
    - “C-F” miscellaneous, 1967-1998, (4 folders)
    - Goode, Wilson W., 1985-1988, undated
    - Gray, William H., 1978-1992, undated
    - “G” miscellaneous, 1985-1989, 1995
    - Hunter, Alberta, 1979-1984
    - “H” miscellaneous, 1980-1995
    - Ince, Earl, 1983
    - “J” miscellaneous, 1978-1985
    - Klock, Kathleen, 1983, 1992-1997, undated
    - “K” miscellaneous, 1984-1988, 1994 (Box 77)
    - Lawyers
      - Alexander, Raymond Pace, 1928, 1971-1975, 1986
      - Alexander, Sadie T. M., 1928, 1963-1970, undated See also Containers 54 and 55, Estates
      - “A” miscellaneous, 1976-1995
      - Binns, James J., 1997
      - “B” miscellaneous, 1975-1992
      - Capers, Jean Murrell, 1985-1986, 1992, undated
      - “C-F” miscellaneous, 1975-1994, (2 folders)
      - Guinier, Lani, 1991-1993, undated
      - “G” miscellaneous, 1976, 1993-1997
      - Harris, Patricia Roberts, 1965, 1982-1985, undated
      - Hastie, William H., 1964-1969, 1975-1985, undated (Box 78)
      - Houston, Charles H.
        - Correspondence, 1949, undated
        - Miscellany, 1935-1939, 1950, 1974, 1984-1994, undated, (3 folders)
      - “H- K” miscellaneous, 1971-1995, undated, (2 folders)
      - Lotman, Arlene J.
        - Miscellany, 1972-1974, 1992-1993, undated
        - Sandra Day O'Connor Award packet, 1993
      - “L” miscellaneous, 1965, undated
      - Moore, Cecil B., 1962-1979, 1986, undated
      - Morton-Finney, John, 1935, 1986-1991, undated (Box 79)
      - “M” miscellaneous, 1963-1983, 1997
      - Nix, Robert N. C., 1981-1985, 1995, undated
      - “N-R” miscellaneous, 1992-1998, undated, (4 folders)
      - Smith, J. Clay, 1984, undated
      - Smith, J. Ryan, 1993, undated